A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, SG 1.24 (A98) FA1295
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, SG 1.24 (A98)
1918-1998
1988-1998
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA1295
154.82 Cubic Feet Standard record storage boxes, R3073-R3190
Conditions Governing Access
Files with entire contents more than 20 years old are available for research. All inquiries require advanced notice of at least 2 business days, and may necessitate notice of up to one week.
Biographical / Historical
The Rockefeller Foundation was established by act of the New York State Legislature approved by the Governor on May 14, 1913, "to promote the well-being of mankind throughout the world." Between 1913 and 1928 the China Medical Board, the International Health Board, and the Division of Medical Education functioned as divisions of the Foundation, concentrating on the administration of programs in public health and medical education. A Division of Studies was created in 1923 to handle projects outside the medical field. These early years were experimental as the new foundation studied the methods of philanthropy and explored its relationships with other Rockefeller boards. Although the Rockefeller Foundation is the largest and best known philanthropy founded by the Rockefeller family, it was neither the first nor the last to be established. The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (1901), the General Education Board (1902), the Rockefeller Sanitary Commission for the Eradication of Hookworm Disease (1909), and the Bureau of Social Hygiene (1911) all existed earlier. When the Foundation was created, the Sanitary Commission was disbanded. After the establishment of the Foundation, the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (1918) and the International Education Board (1923) were created.
The Rockefeller boards and their programs were reconsidered and reorganized in 1927-1928 in order to avoid overlapping programs. The International Health Board of the Foundation was disbanded and an International Health Division was organized. The China Medical Board, Inc., was established as a separately incorporated institution, and the China Medical Board of the Foundation ceased to exist. The Division of Studies was dropped and the Division of Medical Education was phased out. The Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial was combined with the Foundation and the Spelman Fund of New York was chartered to continue activities of the LSRM that were not absorbed by the Foundation. The International Education Board was disbanded.
As a result of this reorganization, the Foundation adopted a program which included public health work (administered by the IHD), the advancement of knowledge in the medical and natural sciences (in part taken over from the IEB), the social sciences (formerly the field of the LSRM), and the humanities and arts (shared with the GEB). The Rockefeller Institute and the Bureau of Social Hygiene were not affected by the reorganization. The program adopted by the Foundation at this time remained basically the same for the next twenty years.
Arrangement
Reccords are primarily arranged by Program.
Some subgroups may contain portions of the material that are arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Other Finding Aids
or other open RF project files, please refer to the following findng aids:
FA386 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.1
FA387 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.2
FA388 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3
FA209 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3-1.8
FA479 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-1.15
FA469 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.16-1.19
FA471 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.20-1.23
FA477 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.25
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1998.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: project files as well as program and policy files.
- Program and Policy - Arts, 1973-1992; 925
  - Carnegie Hall Society - Music Competition, 1979-1992 (Box R3073)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes supplementary material.
  - Carnegie Hall Society - Music Competition, 1979-1992 (Box R3074)
  - Music - Fellowships, 1973-1983; 1989 (Box R3075)
  - Music - Fellowships, 1973-1983; 1989 (Box R3076)
  - Music - Fellowships, 1973-1983; 1989 (Box R3077)
  - Music - Fellowships - Piano Competition Tapes, 1973-1983; 1989 (Box R3078)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copy currently unavailable. See a RAC archivist for further assistance.
  - Music - Fellowships - European Tour, 1981-1983 (Box R3079)
  - Music - Fellowships - Gowen, 1978-1986 (Box R3079)
  - Music - Fellowships - Fulkerson, 1980-1986 (Box R3079)
  - Music - Fellowships - Hodgkinson, 1981-1984; 1987 (Box R3079)
  - Music - Fellowships - Parker, 1979-1985 (Box R3079)
  - Music - Fellowships - Le Dizes-Richard, 1984 (Box R3079)
  - Music - Fellowships - European Tour - Stillman, 1981-1983 (Box R3079)
- Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1989-1997; 120
  - Scholars - Adamu, Abdalla Uba, 1992-1994 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Akenson, Donald Harman, 1992-1993 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Alves, Rubem A., 1991-1995 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Aman, Alfred C., Jr., 1992-1994 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Amar, Georges, 1992-1993 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Amos, Emma, 1992-1993 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Appleton, Jon Howard, 1992-1995 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Atmanspacher, Harald, 1992-1993 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Bell, Dozier, 1992-1995 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Beshir, Mahdi, 1992-1995 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Biasiny-Revera, Charles, 1992-1994 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Biscardi, Chester, 1991-1995 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Blumenthal, Eileen, 1992-1993 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Brewbaker, James Lynn, 1992-1993 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Buck-Morss, Susan, 1992-1993 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Burch, Eva (Co-Researchers - Krysztof Zanussi, Robert Hollander), 1993-1994 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Burko, Diane, 1992-1994 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Carse, James Pearce, 1991-1995 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Cassells, Cyrus, 1992-1995 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Cave, Roderick, 1992-1994 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Cernea, Michael M., 1992-1994 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Chandra, Sudhir, 1992-1994 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Cobbinah, Joseph Rexford, 1992-1994 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Csikszenthmihalyi, Mihaly, 1992-1994 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Czarniawska-Jorges, Barbara (Co Resident - Bernward Joerges), 1992-1993 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Czerniawski, Adam, 1992-1997 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Dalal, Ajit Kumar, 1992-1993 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Davidson, Arnold Edward, 1992-1993 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Davidson, Cathy N., 1992-1993 (Box R3080)
  - Scholars - Debicki, Andrew P., 1991-1994 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Delgado, Richard (Co-Resident - Jean Stefancic, 1992-1997 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - De Ungria, Ricardo M., 1992-1994; 1997 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Diesendruck, Tamar, 1992-1993 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Dobash, Rebecca Emerson (Co-Residents: Russell P. Dobash, Margo Ings Wilson, Martin Daly, 1992-1993 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Eady, Cornelius, 1992-1995 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Eaton, John C., 1990-1994 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Economou, George Demetrios, 1992-1993; 1997-1998 (Box R3081)
    Restricted - Open in 2019.
  - Scholars - Fanger, Donald, 1991-1993 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Figueroa, John J. M., 1992-1993 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Frankenberg, Gunther, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Friendlander, Dov, 1992-1993 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Friedman, Barry, 1992-1994 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Gardner, Howard E., 1992-1993 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Garrison, Willam T., 1992-1995 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Giele, Janet Zollinger, 1992-1995 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Geodicke, Patricia, 1992-1993; 1997 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Goodrich, Diana Sorensen, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Gordon, Wendy J., 1992-1994 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Graham, Lawrence S., 1992-1993 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Graziano, Frank, 1992-1993 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Greenhouse, Carol J., 1992-1993 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Hagen, Daron Aric, 1992-1994 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Handler, Joel F., 1991-1993; 1996 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Hasenfeld, Yeheskel Zeke, 1992-1993 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Hastings, John Woodland, 1992-1993 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Haynes, Robert Brian, 1992-1993 (Box R3081)
  - Scholars - Hecht, Anthony Evan, 1992-1993 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Herbert, James, 1992-1994 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Hetzel, Basil Stuart, 1992-1994 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Higgins, Kathleen Marie, 1992-1994 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Horowitz, Mardi J., 1992-1993 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Hutcheon, Linda (Co-Resident - Michael Alexander Hutcheon), 1992-1995 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Ickstadt, Heinrich M., 1992-1993 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Jacoff, Rachel, 1992-1995 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Jaimes, Marie Annette, 1992-1993 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Jose, Francisco Sionil, 1992-1993 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Judt, Tony Robert, 1992-1993 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Kavale, Kenneth A., 1992-1996 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Katzman, David M., 1992-1994 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Keohane, Robert Owen, 1992-1996 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Kim, Choong Soon, 1992-1996 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Kirova, Milena Georgieva, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Kohler, Henning, 1992-1993 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Krislov, Samuel, 1992-1993 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Lapidoth, Ruth, 1989-1993; 1997 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Lee, Valerie E., 1992-1993 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Lieberthal, Kenneth Guy, 1992-1993 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Linhares Barsted, Leila de Andrade, 1992-1994 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Luzuriaga, Diego, 1991-1995 (Box R3082)
  - Scholars - Macleod, Stuart Maxwell, 1992-1995 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - McIntosh, Kenneth, 1992-1994 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - McIntosh, Peggy, 1992-1994 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - McKay, Alexander Gordon, 1992-1993 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - McNair, Wesley, 1992-1995 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Majok, Aggrey Ayuen (Co-Resident - Calvin W. Schwabe, 1992-1996 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Marriage, Alwyn, 1992-1993 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Medsger, Betty, 1992-1997 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Meyers, Diana Tietjens, 1992-1994 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Micale, Mark Stephen, 1992-1993 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Miller, Edward Jay, 1991-1994 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Miller, Marvin M., 1992-1993 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Minear, Larry (Co-Resident - Thomas G. Weiss), 1992-1995 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Moe, Eric, 1992-1993 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Mukherjee, Meenakshi, 1991-1993 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Naheed Kishwar, 1992-1994 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - O'Grada, Cormac, 1991-1992 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Orru, Marco, 1992-1993 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Owens, Rochelle, 1992-1994; 1997 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Pardo de Velez, Graciela (Co-Resident - Marlene Cedano Collazos), 1992-1994 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Parker, Frank R., 1992-1993 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Paxton, Robert O., 1992-1993 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Quinn, Susan Taft, 1992-1995 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Richter, Irving (Did Not Go), 1989 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Rivera Marin, Guadalupe, 1992-1997 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Rose, Thomas A. (Co-Residents - Don Belton, David Alan Mura, Maria Cheng), 1992-1993 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Ross, John Munder, 1992-1994 (Box R3083)
  - Scholars - Schapiro, Miriam, 1992-1995 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Schulman, Howard, 1991-1994 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Segre, Daniel Vittorio, 1992-1993 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Sen, Nabaneeta Dev, 1992-1993 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Shea, Judith, 1992-1993 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Simpson, Mona, 1992-1994 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Sitesh, Aruna, 1992-1994 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Sivaraksa, Sulak, 1992-1993 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Smith, Anna Deavre, 1992-1994 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Smith-Rosenberg, Carroll, 1992-1994 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Solomon, Robert C., 1992-1995 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Spence, Sarah, 1992-1994 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Stary, Zdenek, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Stern, Richard G., 1992-1993 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Strand, Mark, 1992-1994 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Teitelbaum, Michael Stewart (Co-Resident - Jay Murray Winter), 1992-1994 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Tham, Carl, 1992-1994 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Thompson, Esme, 1992-1993 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Tilly, Richard, 1992-1994 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Valdes, Juan Gabriel, 1992-1994 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Van Sickle, John, 1992-1993 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Wan Fang, 1992-1995 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Weinstein, Donald, 1992-1994 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Whelan, Richard, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - White, Edmund, 1992-1993 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Wijesinha, Rajiva, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Wilkerson, Margaret B., 1992-1993 (Box R3084)
  - Scholars - Wink, Andre, 1991-1993 (Box R3085)
  - Scholars - Wood, Gordon S., 1992-1993 (Box R3085)
  - Scholars - Yadava, Yogendra Prasad, 1992-1994 (Box R3085)
  - Scholars - Ziolkowski, Theodore, 1992-1993 (Box R3085)
  - Scholars - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe, 1992-1993 (Box R3085)
  - Characterization of Fungal Pathogens of Sorghum and Millet - Conference, 1991-1995 (Box R3085)
  - Children's Vaccine Initiative Ad Hoc Committee on an Investment Strategy for Measles Control - Conference, 1992-1995 (Box R3085)
  - Civil Society in the Middle East - Conference, 1992-1995 (Box R3085)
  - Domestic Institutions, Free Trade and the Pressures for National Conference - U.S., Europe, Japan - Conference, 1991-1993 (Box R3085)
  - Donor Collaboration on Agenda 21 Research and Capacity Building Initiatives - Conference, 1992-1994 (Box R3085)
  - Environmental History: South-Asian Perspectives - Conference, 1990-1992 (Box R3085)
  - European Security After German Unity and CFE - Conference, 1990-1992 (Box R3085)
  - Forum on Population and Development - Conference, 1989-1991 (Box R3085)
  - Gender and War - Conference, 1992-1993 (Box R3085)
  - Group of Donors Interested in African Publishing - Conference, 1992-1995 (Box R3085)
  - Health of School Age Children - Conference, 1991-1992 (Box R3085)
  - Internationalization of Civil Society and the Public Sphere - Conference, 1992-1994 (Box R3085)
  - Literature, Ethnocentrism and Pluralism: Comparative Literacy History in the 21st Century - Conference, 1992-1996 (Box R3085)
  - Malaria and Ecosystems: Historical Aspects - Conference, 1992-1995 (Box R3086)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - BC Conference: Managing Transition to Global Climate Change Regime, 1990-1993 (Box R3086)
  - Meeting Women's Needs for Post-Abortion Family Planning - Conference, 1991-1994 (Box R3086)
  - Middle East Arms Control After the Israeli-PLO Agreement - Conference, 1992-1994 (Box R3086)
  - Network of Sorghum and Millet Experts - Conference, 1990-1991 (Box R3086)
  - Nomenclature of Sequenced Plant Genes - Conference, 1991-1994 (Box R3086)
  - Panel on Population Policies - Conference, 1993 (Box R3086)
  - Planning and Coordinating Committee for Forum for Sustainable Development - Conference, 1993 (Box R3086)
  - Pluralism and its Cultural Expressions: Journals of Opinion and the Civil Society - Conference, 1993 (Box R3086)
  - Preserving the Intellectual Heritage - Conference, 1992-1994 (Box R3086)
  - Real Wages, Migration and Labor Market Integration Conference, 1992-1995 (Box R3086)
  - Recasting Intellectual History: African-American Cultural Studies - Conference, 1992-1994 (Box R3086)
  - RF 91009 A 3 - Rockefeller Foundation - BC Conference: Pesticides, Environment and Health, 1991-1992; 1996 (Box R3086)
  - Reexamining Foreign Aid: Crisis in Development Cooperation - Conference, 1993 (Box R3086)
  - Sexually Transmitted Diseases Prize Workshop, 1993-1994 (Box R3086)
  - Strengthening Tropical Infectious Disease Research and Control - Conference, 1993-1994 (Box R3086)
  - Tata Energy Research Institute - BC Conference: Review Study on Greenhouse Gas Emissions of Asia and Brazil, 1989-1994 (Box R3086)
- Rockefeller Foundation (RF), 1983-1998
  - RF 86054 A 2 - University of the Philippines - Economics - Faculty Retention-Recruitment, 1986-1995 (Box R3087)
  - RF 87058 A 77 - International Rice Research Institute - Bacillus Thuringiensis, 1987-1990 (Box R3087)
  - RF 880838 A 76 - Nangendo, Stevie Moses, 1988-1994; 1997 (Box R3087)
  - RF 88048 - Gender Role Changes, 1983-1993 (Box R3087)
  - RF 88048 - Gender Role Changes, 1983-1993 (Box R3088)
  - RF 88048 - Gender Role Changes, 1983-1993 (Box R3089)
  - RF 88048 - Gender Role Changes - Video, 1983-1993 (Box R3089)
  - RF 88048 A 82 - Riley, E. Denise, 1988-1994 (Box R3090)
  - RF 88060 - World Wildlife Fund - Forest Policies in Developing Countries, 1988-1993 (Box R3090)
  - RF 88072 A 12 - Columbia University - Seminar Series on Perceptions of Africa, 1991-1995 (Box R3090)
  - RF 88076 - AIDS Initiatives in Africa, 1988 (Box R3090)
  - RF 88077 - Latin American Population Sciences Network, 1988 (Box R3090)
  - RF 88078 A 59 - Nigerian Insitute of Social and Economic Research - Population Policy, 1989-1995 (Box R3090)
  - RF 88078 A 62 - Corner, Lorraine, 1989-1996 (Box R3091)
  - RF 88079 A 261 - Presser, Harriet B., 1989-1996 (Box R3091)
  - RF 89014 A 446 - University of Texas, Austin - Resident Fellows (Latin American Studies), 1988-1996 (Box R3091)
  - RF 89014 A 448 - University of California, Los Angeles - Resident Fellows (Asian American Studies), 1989-1994 (Box R3091)
  - RF 89026 A 20 - - Kasetsart University - Ragged Stunt Virus Resistance, 1989-1994 (Box R3091)
  - RF 89026 A 23 - Kasetsart University - Wide Hybridization, 1989; 1992-1995 (Box R3091)
  - RF 89026 A 45 - United Nations Industrial Development Organization - Lab Courses at ICCEB, 1990-1996 (Box R3091)
  - RF 89026 A 48 - University of Calcutta - RFLP Probes, 1989-1993; 1996 (Box R3091)
  - RF 89027 A 9 - International Rice Research Institute - Modern Rice Technology in Tamil Nadu, 1986-1994 (Box R3092)
  - RF 89027 A 9 - International Rice Research Institute - Modern Rice Technology in Tamil Nadu - Supplementary Material, 1986-1994 (Box R3092)
  - RF 89028 A 229 - Javeriana University - White Coat Hypertension, 1990-1993 (Box R3092)
  - RF 89033 A 52 - Peking University - Fertility Patterns in Inner Mongolia, 1990-1993; 1996 (Box R3092)
  - RF 89057 A 106 - Okereke, Gilbert Uwahamaka, 1990-1995 (Box R3092)
  - RF 89057 A 116 - Jameel, Shahid, 1989-1995; 1998 (Box R3092)
  - RF 89057 A 117 - Kamboj, Kamal K., 1990; 1993-1995 (Box R3092)
  - RF 89057 A 120 - Kasbekar, Durgadas Prabhakar, 1990-1996 (Box R3092)
  - RF 89057 A 121 - Raymundo, Asuncion K., 1990-1994 (Box R3092)
  - RF 89057 A 122 - Zhang Qifa, 1990-1992; 1995 (Box R3093)
  - RF 89057 A 123 - Andreo, Carlos Santiago, 1990-1995 (Box R3093)
  - RF 89057 A 126 - Low Fee-Chon, 1987-1991; 1997 (Box R3093)
  - RF 89092 A 67 - Feyisetan, Bamikale James, 1989-1996 (Box R3093)
  - RF 89092 A 82 - Khasiani, Shanyisa A., 1990-1996 (Box R3093)
  - RF 89092 A 90 - Van de Walle, Etienne - Demand for Children in Tanzania, 1990-1995 (Box R3093)
  - RF 89094 A 3 - Schoenly, Kenneth, 1990-1994 (Box R3093)
  - RF 89094 A 7 - Bronson, Kevin F. - Measuring and Modeling Methane Fluxes, 1991-1994 (Box R3093)
  - RF 89094 A 8 - International Laboratory for Research in Animal Diseases (ILRAD) - Environmental Implications of Controlling Tstetse-Transmitted Trypanosomiasis, 1992-1994 (Box R3093)
  - RF 89094 A 9 - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center (CIMMYT) - Effects of Soil and Crop Management on Productivity and Quality of Soil, 1992-1994 (Box R3094)
  - RF 90003 A 456 - Northwestern University - Resident Fellows, 1989-1994 (Box R3094)
  - RF 90003 A 459 - State University of New York at Buffalo - Resident Fellows (American Studies), 1990-1995 (Box R3094)
  - RF 90003 A 460 - University of Chicago - Resident Fellows (South Asia), 1989-1995 (Box R3094)
  - RF 90003 A 461 - City College - Resident Fellows, 1990-1994 (Box R3094)
  - RF 90003 A 463 - University of Oaklahoma - Resident Fellows, 1987-1995 (Box R3094)
  - RF 90003 A 464 - University of Iowa - Resident Fellows, 1986-1995 (Box R3094)
  - RF 90003 A 465 - University of California (Berkeley) - Resident Fellows, 1987-1995 (Box R3095)
  - RF 90003 A 467 - Indiana University - Resident Fellows (Inner Asian Studies), 1989-1994 (Box R3095)
  - RF 90006 A 5 - Corporation for the Advancement of Policy Evaluation - Child Outcomes, 1990-1993; 1997 (Box R3095)
  - RF 90031 A 108 - University of Washington - Rice Tungro Agroinfection, 1990-1994 (Box R3095)
  - RF 90031 A 110 - National Instititute for Agricultural Research (France) - Agrobacterium Rhizongenes, 1990-1994 (Box R3095)
  - RF 90031 A 117 - Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization - Genetic Variation in Rice, 1990-1995 (Box R3095)
  - RF 90031 A 121 - Stanford University - Rice Genetic Engineering, 1984-1995 (Box R3095)
  - RF 90034 A 80 - Tel Aviv University - Gossypol Effects, 1990-1993 (Box R3095)
  - RF 90034 A 81 - Zhejiang Academy of Medical Sciences - Gossypol Enzymes and Sterility, 1991-1996 (Box R3095)
  - RF 90038 A 180 - Mukisira, Ephraim Amiani, 1990-1994; 1997 (Box R3096)
  - RF 90051 A 8 - Dong Jinjiang, 1990-1994 (Box R3096)
  - RF 90053 A 55 - Chung, Kimberly Rae, 1991-1996 (Box R3096)
  - RF 90062 - National Public Radio - Cultural Programs, 1989-1995 (Box R3096)
  - RF 90063 A 73 - Jersey, W.C. (Bill), 1990-1994 (Box R3096)
  - RF 90069 - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation - Reproductive Freedom, 1989-1992 (Box R3096)
  - RF 90079 A 4 - Mexican Foundation for Health - Advisory Board Use, 1988-1996 (Box R3096)
  - RF 90079 A 4 - Mexican Foundation for Health - Advisory Board Use, 1988-1996 (Box R3097)
  - RF 90080 A 14 - Population Council, Inc. - Sexual Transmission of HIV Across Epithelia, 1990-1993; 1996 (Box R3097)
  - RF 90083 A 65 - Catholic University (Chile) - Endocrinology Training, 1989-1993; 1997 (Box R3097)
  - RF 90083 A 70 - International Organization for Research in Reproductive Health (Brazil), 1993-1994 (Box R3097)
  - RF 90083 A 71 - Association Dominicana Pro-Bienestar de La Familia, Inc. - Training and Networking at Department of Biomedical Research, 1993-1995 (Box R3097)
  - RF 90086 A 269 - Weinstein, Maxine, 1990-1993; 1996 (Box R3097)
  - RF 90086 A 274 - Degraff, Deborah S., 1990-1994 (Box R3097)
  - RF 90099 A 91 - Randolph Street Gallery - Production of New York, 1991-1993 (Box R3097)
  - RF 90113 - Grameen Trust - Micro-Credit and Social Development Program, 1990-1998 (Box R3097)
  - RF 90114 - Africa News Service, Inc., 1987-1992 (Box R3098)
  - RF 91001 A 132 - University of Montreal - Betaine Accumulation in Rice, 1990-1994; 1997 (Box R3098)
  - RF 91001 A 141 - Jefferson, Richard Anthony - Rice Transformation Vectors and Assay Systems Dissemination to Developing Countries, 1991-1993; 1997 (Box R3098)
  - RF 91003 A 86 - University of Rio de Janeiro - Molecular Analysis in Rice, 1990-1996 (Box R3098)
  - RF 91003 A 101 - Hunan Academy of Agricultural Sciences - Apomixis in Rice, 1990-1993; 1996 (Box R3098)
  - RF 91003 A 104 - Sichuan Agricultural University - Apomixis in Rice, 1990-1996 (Box R3098)
  - RF 91003 A 116 - University of Philippines - Rice Biotech Program, 1988-1993; 1996 (Box R3098)